export const QuizData = [
  //Lesson 1
  {
    id: 0,
    question: "右",
    choices: ["sun", "moon", "right", "left"],
    answer: "right",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "円",
    choices: ["sun", "yen", "king", "noise"],
    answer: "yen",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "花",
    choices: ["flower", "down", "science", "fire"],
    answer: "flower",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "音",
    choices: ["school", "sound", "spirit", "left"],
    answer: "sound",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "気",
    choices: ["circle", "down", "spirit", "rain"],
    answer: "spirit",
  },
  //Lesson 2
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "休",
    choices: ["ball", "gold", "rest", "nine"],
    answer: "rest",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "空",
    choices: ["sun", "sky", "spirit", "noise"],
    answer: "sky",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "犬",
    choices: ["opinion", "five", "science", "dog"],
    answer: "dog",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "口",
    choices: ["sun", "sound", "mouth", "dog"],
    answer: "mouth",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "月",
    choices: ["circle", "month", "year", "rain"],
    answer: "month",
  },

  //Lesson 3
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "校",
    choices: ["school", "gold", "left", "nine"],
    answer: "school",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "山",
    choices: ["sun", "mountain", "child", "noise"],
    answer: "mountain",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "糸",
    choices: ["letter", "ear", "thread", "dog"],
    answer: "thread",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "車",
    choices: ["hand", "child", "mouth", "car"],
    answer: "car",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "手",
    choices: ["hand", "month", "year", "mouth"],
    answer: "hand",
  },
  //Lesson 4
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "女",
    choices: ["woman", "man", "left", "right"],
    answer: "woman",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "小",
    choices: ["up", "small", "child", "noise"],
    answer: "small",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "森",
    choices: ["letter", "forest", "person", "dog"],
    answer: "forest",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "水",
    choices: ["water", "person", "life", "car"],
    answer: "water",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "青",
    choices: ["hand", "blue", "red", "mouth"],
    answer: "blue",
  },

  //Lesson 5
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "赤",
    choices: ["blue", "red", "left", "right"],
    answer: "red",
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: "先",
    choices: ["up", "before", "down", "river"],
    answer: "before",
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "川",
    choices: ["dog", "forest", "person", "river"],
    answer: "river",
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: "草",
    choices: ["water", "grass", "forest", "river"],
    answer: "grass",
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "村",
    choices: ["village", "mouth", "leg", "bamboo"],
    answer: "village",
  },

  //Lesson 6
  {
    id: 25,
    question: "町",
    choices: ["village", "town", "left", "right"],
    answer: "town",
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: "天",
    choices: ["up", "spirit", "down", "sky"],
    answer: "sky",
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: "日",
    choices: ["day", "moon", "insect", "river"],
    answer: "day",
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: "年",
    choices: ["sun", "month", "year", "river"],
    answer: "year",
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question: "田",
    choices: ["village", "rice field", "town", "bamboo"],
    answer: "village",
  },
  //Lesson 7
  {
    id: 30,
    question: "白",
    choices: ["white", "red", "blue", "black"],
    answer: "white",
  },
  {
    id: 31,
    question: "文",
    choices: ["word", "sentence", "down", "up"],
    answer: "sentence",
  },
  {
    id: 32,
    question: "本",
    choices: ["tree", "book", "person", "dog"],
    answer: "book",
  },
  {
    id: 33,
    question: "名",
    choices: ["name", "month", "year", "person"],
    answer: "year",
  },
  {
    id: 34,
    question: "目",
    choices: ["hand", "eye", "foot", "mouth"],
    answer: "eye",
  },
  //Lesson 8
  {
    id: 35,
    question: "豉",
    choices: ["park", "beans", "far", "black"],
    answer: "beans",
  },
  {
    id: 36,
    question: "黄",
    choices: ["white", "yellow", "red", "green"],
    answer: "yellow",
  },
  {
    id: 37,
    question: "何",
    choices: ["tree", "house", "what", "meeting"],
    answer: "what",
  },
  {
    id: 38,
    question: "会",
    choices: ["meeting", "month", "year", "park"],
    answer: "meeting",
  },
  {
    id: 39,
    question: "力",
    choices: ["hand", "power", "tree", "water"],
    answer: "power",
  },
];
